9343879v.5

PRIVACY STATEMENT

Prizmah is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement, which is part of ourTerms of Use [also available on Prizmah.org], describes the information we collect throughwww.prizmah.org (“Our Site”), how we use and share it, and how you can make choices aboutour use of that information.

By using Our Site, you consent to our collection, use, and sharing of information asdescribed in these Terms of Use.

Collection of Personal Information

We collect personally identifiable information about you (“Personal Information”), such as yourname, email address, mailing address, phone number, profession and employment, and otherinformation, when you voluntarily provide it to us. For instance, we may collect PersonalInformation when you sign up for the Prizmah email mailing list, register as a professional or layleader of a Prizmah member school, or subscribe to Prizmah’s journal, HaYidion. We may alsocollect Personal Information about others (such as names and emails), which you voluntarilyprovide, to encourage them to participate in Prizmah activities, such as registering for a Prizmahconference or signing up for our email mailing list. If you provide any Personal Informationabout others, you agree that you have the right and permission from those individuals to providesuch information and for Prizmah to collect and use that Personal Information for the purpose forwhich it was provided.

We will use your Personal Information for the purposes for which you provided it. You agreethat we may also send you information about news, events, or opportunities that we think may beof interest to you. If you no longer wish to receive communications from us, you canunsubscribe by (i) clicking on the “unsubscribe” button in the email you receive from us;(ii) changing your preferences in your Account profile; (iii) emailing us at hello@prizmah.org, or(iv) calling us at 646-975-2800.

Other Information; Cookies and Other Technologies

We may also collect other information about visitors to Our Site, such as the time and date ofvisits to Our Site, the length of the visit, the web pages viewed during a visit, the links followed,the order of pages viewed, the type of web browser used, the web site that referred or linked youto Our Site, the web site you visited upon leaving Our Site, the domain name associated withyour computer, and the IP address associated with your computer (which is the number assignedto the visitor’s computer to identify its location on the Internet).

We collect some of this information through cookies which are small data files placed on yourcomputer. You are not required to accept cookies from Our Site and may disable the cookiesfunction, or delete existing cookies, by using your web browser’s options. If you disablecookies, certain features of Our Site may not work as intended. We may use this information toanalyze how visitors use Our Site so we can improve the quality of the information and serviceswe provide.

Prizmah: Center for Jewish Day Schools 2017

We and our Service Providers may also use clear GIFs (also known as web beacons, web bugs orspotlight or pixel tags) and similar technologies (collectively, “Technologies”) in connectionwith the Site for such purposes as tracking the activities of visitors to compile statistics aboutSite usage and enhance the experience of our visitors. We and our Service Providers also mayuse Technologies in HTML-formatted e-mail messages to help us track e-mail response rates,measure the success of our marketing campaigns, and identify when our e-mails are viewed orforwarded. These Technologies are generally tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar infunction to cookies. However, in contrast to cookies, which are stored on your computer's harddrive, clear GIFs are embedded invisibly on website pages.

We do not use information derived from cookies or Technologies to identify visitors individuallyexcept in circumstances where we may deem it necessary in connection with legal process or toprotect our rights or the rights of a third party as further described below.

Sharing Information with Third Parties

We may share your Personal Information with our service providers that help us operate andprovide services in connection with Our Site (“Service Providers”). We reserve the right todisclose and use Personal Information and other information in special circumstances, includingto enforce this Privacy Statement or any other part of our Terms of Use, to comply with legalprocess or law enforcement, to address actual or suspected illegal activity, to protect our propertyor rights; to protect the rights and safety of anyone, or for other reasons we determine in goodfaith are necessary, appropriate, or required by law. Of course, if we ever spin off as a separateentity, merge with, are acquired by, or otherwise consolidate with another organization, PersonalInformation may be transferred along with our other assets.

Links to Third-Party Web Sites

Our Site may contain links to Third-Party Web Sites and content providers. If you follow anylink to a third-party site, you should review those sites’ privacy statements to find out how theyprotect your privacy. We are not responsible for Third-Party Web Sites or their privacypractices.

Any online payments to Prizmah will be made through a link to Paypal, a Third Party Web Site,and subject to Paypal’s privacy practices and terms of use.

Security

We use reasonable efforts to safeguard your Personal Information. All transmissions to Our Site,including transmission of Personal Information, are secured and encrypted. Of course notransmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, so you provide yourPersonal Information at your own risk.

Prizmah: Center for Jewish Day Schools 2017

Review and Update Your Personal Information

If you wish to review and update your Personal Information, you can do so by logging onto yourRegistered User Account.

Location of Servers and Transfer of Information

Our servers are located in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, beaware that the information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By usingOur Site or providing your Personal Information to us, you consent to this transfer and to thecollection, storage, processing and use of your Personal Information in the United States. If youare located in the United States, our Service Providers may not be located in your geographicarea in the United States. By providing your Personal Information on Our Site, you consent tothe transfer of your Personal Information to these Service Providers.

Children Under Age 13

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of13\. If you are a parent or guardian and you believe that your child under age 13 may haveprovided personally identifiable information through Our Site, please contact our web team athello@prizmah.org.

Questions

For any questions you may have about this Privacy Statement, please contact our web team athello@prizmah.org.
